Research method category:
Environmental data AND/OR Information solicitation task

Specific question:
If we would automatically or already know the contiguity of communities along the coastline (this would be known data if it were “this world” or anywhere publicly mapped in any world), then we request the full map of associations between areas and with respect to the coast, storm, each other, and other Hurricane-path-relevant geographical features (e.g., mountains, ridges, other water bodies, etc.; as would be available from the U.S. Geographical Survey and NOAA). 

If that is not considered an independent data request, then
in addition to that geo-spatial information, we request the complete results of the survey data from the survey reported to have been performed before and after Hurricane season for all individuals surveyed in the region, with before and after survey responses linked by individual, and response rates indexed by region and any finer geographical data available.

Sampling strategy:
Insofar as this is an information solicitation on existing environmental and/or previously collected survey data, we request data on the entire environment, and the entire population surveyed from the region. If this is not possible or forthcoming, we seek this information on a random sample the population, of maximal size that we can afford.

Other applicable detail:
We seek any environmental data that could bear on the movement and impact of hurricanes. 

Research request priority:
10 (on 1-10 scale; critical)




